stripteasecomic.com 2014-06-29

# Keenspot.com: Privacy Policy

PRIVACY POLICY  
Keenspot does not collect information from its visitors without their knowledge. Keenspot may request demographic and poll information from its visitors, but participation is completely optional. Whatever the case, the personal information you supply, if you choose to do so, will not be given out or sold under any circumstances.

Occasionally we will ask you for personal information, such as your name, email address, address, etc. when you sign up for various services such as 

[Keenspot PREMIUM](https://premium/), or an account on our [Forums](http://forums.keenspot.com/) or when you buy items from our Store. This information is only used for your security to identify you and protect your account access and information. It is never shared or sold to any other company.Keenspot works with a number of third party companies that serve ads to our network of sites. To find out more about how these companies manage the privacy of information in conjunction with serving ads on this site, please go to:  

We use outside ad companies to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our advertisers, and we do not have access to this information. These companies may use the information (which does not include your name, address, email, or telephone number) collected in these cookies to provide you advertisements for goods and services which most appropriately suit your interests. You may choose not to have your information shared through these cookies to third party advertisers through their various opt-out programs. For information on opting out of the Doubleclick program, go to their [Opt Out](http://www.doubleclick.net/us/corporate/privacy/privacy/ad-cookie/default.asp?asp_object_1=&) webpage.

This site contains links to other sites. 

Keenspot is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. Contacting the Web Site - If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact: [keenspot @keenspot.com](mailto:keenspot@keenspot.com "email us.")

**3/19/2002 ADDENDUM:** In the interests of meeting Doubleclick's and/or MaxWorldWide's privacy policy policies more expediently, we have inserted the following required verbiage, which may be highly redundant with the information above: 

**Third Party Advertising:** We use MaxWorldWide, DoubleClick and other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please click [Here.](http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp)

**Third Party Cookies:** In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser. 

Keenspot.com welcomes your questions and comments about privacy. Please send e-mail to [privacy @keenspot.com](mailto:privacy@keenspot.com "email us.")
